### Rob Grabowski

UX/UI Designer & Developer

rob.j.grabowski@gmail.com (781) 296 - 7362 robgrabowski.com Experienced Designer & Developer advocating for the user. I believe the user is always at the core of design. I make websites and mobile apps usable so companies get more value from their customers.

EXPERIENCE

### Freelance Designer

January 2017 - Current

Consultant

I work with a variety of clients designing and developing their websites.

#### Your Private Eyestylist

- Worked with client to refine business objectives through meetings and a business/brand questionaire.
- To understand potential customers I conducted a User Survey.
- From the User Survey results I created User Personas and User Flow Diagrams.
- Created a Site map and did a content analysis based on the business offerings.
- Designed High-Fidelity Wireframes.
- Presented mockups with Typeface and Color Palette options.
- Developed Responsive Home Page with javascript transitions.

#### **Timothy Malone Wines**

- Site redesign for Oregon based wine maker.
- Designed multiple modern wireframe options.
- Used current color palette for design mockups.
- Currently developing site.

#### **FanDistro**

April 2011 - June 2016

Director of Business Development

FanDistro provides an incentive based social media marketing platform for artists and brands. Artists incentivize and reward fans and influencers to amplify the reach and value of their social media campaigns. Brands partner with artists for their campaigns to build brand awareness. FanDistro was named by Midemlab as a 2013 Finalist in the Marketing and Social Engagement category.

- Helped build a business concept from the ground up to an award nominated company.
- Co-managed all aspects of the development cycle including UX/UI Design, Quality Assurance, Front End Development, and Database Design.
- Managed brand ambassador social media marketing campaigns
- Brokered deals between artists and brands.
- Sales outreach.
- Artist and user relations.

## Inflexxion Software Developer

February 2008 - March 2011

- Built content driven websites in C# using an Ektron Content Management System and SQL Server.
- Set up websites to update newsletter lists using Constant Contact's API.
   Developed custom reports using SQL Reporting Services.
- Developed daily tracker questionnaire with printable reports
- using Telerik AJAX controls.

http://robgrabowski.com

Please take a look at my work and connect with me at:

EDUCATION

# West Virginia University B.S., Business Administration, Finance

1990 - 1994

Bloc

2016 - 2017

\_\_\_\_

UX/UI Design

SKILLS

UX/UI Design, Sketch, Adobe Illustrator, Adobe
Photoshop, InvisionApp, Balsamiq, Logo Design, Low/
High Fidelity Wireframing, User Surveys, User Personas,
User Flow Diagrams, Site maps, Mockups, Typeface,
Color, HTML5, CSS, Javascript, JQuery, PHP, C#, ASP.Net,
MySQL, SQL Server